Jawad Alizada

Web Developer (PHP, Laravel, ReactJS) with 3+ years of experience. Strong ownership mindset, proficient in web development technologies, excellent communication and collaboration skills, and a passion for learning and adapting to new technologies.

jawadalizada1@gmail.com +989339435187 LinkedIn

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer | Full time | Onsite

Pooneh Media Des 2022 – June 2023

- Develop and maintain websites using PHP, Joomla, JS jQuery and related technologies.
- Collaborate with front-end developers to integrate front-end and back-end functionalities.
- Translate design concepts into functional code by working with UI/UX designers.
- · Implementing responsive design and ensuring cross-browser compatibility.

Web Developer | Full time | Onsite

Tejaratdaran Farda

Nov 2021 - Nov 2022

- Contributed to developing a centralized software system for dental clinic, including HR, Financial, reception, and main modules.
- The system focused on patients' records, HR and financial department.
- Independently developed 2 modules and collaborated on 3 additional projects.
- Maintaining and adding new features in to existing systems developed on Codelgniter and OpenCart frameworks.

Database Manager | Full time | Onsite

Independent Directorate of Local Governance

Sep 2018 - Aug 2021

- Managed databases for HR records above 30,000 employees.
- · Work closely with developers to assist in database development tasks.
- Support database backup and recovery processes as needed.

EDUCATION

Kabul University, Bachelor in computer science

Afghanistan, Kabul. 2012 - 2016

Qom University of Technologies , Studies Master Degree in Software Engineering

Iran, Qom. 2021 - Now

Languages

Persian: Native English: Fluent

Skills

Front-End: JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, HTML5, CSS3, SASS.

Back-End: PHP, Laravel, SQL, WordPress, Codelgniter.

Tools & Methods: API, PWA, Webpack, Git, GitHub, TDD

Professional: Teamwork, communication, Problem solving, time management.